[{"answer": "I don't have a clue anymore.  I wish you'd talk to him.  He needs a man", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "A man he respects", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Done...close to done", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Fuck the grass.  Who said grass", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Lock the door behind you", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Where he always is", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He never answers", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Because he put the lock on!  Do you think I told him he could have a nose ring?! Why do you ask me everything you should ask him!?  I don't know anything, anymore", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Listen...maybe I can get you a year", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What are you talking about?  You love your job", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend's been feeding him", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I wasn't thinking.  Look, I'm sorry I didn't think to call you while I thought...I think", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "The garage is plumbed.  I'll put in a toilet.  We'll survive", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Sounding?  I need help.  He's cheap labor", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I never said anything.  I haven't done anything", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You don't know what the deal is.  There is no fucking deal", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Your mom and the boys can drop by anytime", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'll be around to check up on you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Why would you be there", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You live in my friend's parents' cabin", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Last time you were gone for a week", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No.  I was going to let you do that", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You got the money", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I wanna be with you today", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "We can work", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm coming in", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We're not gonna do anything", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We're not gonna do anything", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why are you so uptight", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Who are you", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'm his friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm telling you now", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'd be in that place having fun if you had given up", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You can't go with me because of my friend", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "So am I, my friend.  I'm working at something, too.  I'm even talking.  Do you want to be around for it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Let's not do this, okay", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You need to know what?  Do I still love you", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "He's not there", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I checked everywhere.  He's not there", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No.  Mostly me", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Left you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I would have lied to me if I thought I'd believe it", "docId": "LifeAsAHouse.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I never tried to get you to like me.  I tried to get you to love me", "qsentId": 44}]